[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which cities were the original endpoints of the Orient Express railway?", "correct_answer": "Paris and Istanbul", "incorrect_answers": ["Moscow and Vladivostok", "Chicago and Los Angeles", "Tokyo and Kyoto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of aircraft do the Crumps charter to get to Santa Rosita in Its a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World?", "correct_answer": "World War I era biplane", "incorrect_answers": ["hot air balloon", "Lear jet", "helicopter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song by The Beatles, recorded during the Sgt. Pepper sessions, contains the lyrics: \nBehind the shelter in the middle of a roundabout \nThe pretty nurse is selling poppies from a tray?", "correct_answer": "Penny Lane", "incorrect_answers": ["Strawberry Fields Forever", "Help!", "A Hard Days Night"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Opel company was founded in 1863 and began making cars in 1899. What was the first name of its founder Opel?", "correct_answer": "Adam", "incorrect_answers": ["Heinrich", "Friedrich", "Ludwig"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Lex Luthor in Superman: The Movie?", "correct_answer": "Gene Hackman", "incorrect_answers": ["Lyle Talbot", "Kevin Spacey", "Michael Rosenbaum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Joe Pesci appears in the movie Raging Bull.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Star Wars character Chewie is never seen without his bandolier.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In James Bonds Thunderball, what means of communication does the British government use, to let the S.P.E.C.T.R.E. organization know that their terms are acceptable?", "correct_answer": "Big Ben", "incorrect_answers": ["Radio", "Billboard", "Television"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these fruits has a variety called Abraham Lincoln?", "correct_answer": "Tomato", "incorrect_answers": ["Nectarine", "Peach", "Watermelon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1975 television movie, starring James Earl Jones and Estelle Parsons, was based on the supposed abduction in 1961 of an inter racial couple living in New Hampshire.", "correct_answer": "The UFO Incident", "incorrect_answers": ["Alien Autopsy", "X-Files", "Abducted"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was Over Her Dead Body released on DVD in the United States of America?", "correct_answer": "May 6th 2008", "incorrect_answers": ["April 30th 2008", "January 29th 2008", "February 3rd 2008"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The consumption of blood oranges prevents this medical problem.", "correct_answer": "Cataract", "incorrect_answers": ["High blood sugar levels", "High blood pressure", "Insomnia"]}]